Contact

daniellenmoore6@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daniellemoore-bsn-rn-3b527b32 (LinkedIn) shopmyplexus.com/ daniellenmoore/ (Company)

Top Skills

Wound Care
Nursing
Outpatient Surgery

Danielle Moore BSN, RN

Labor & Delivery And Nursery RN (not looking for travel positions or relocating)

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse Labor Delivery with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Post Anesthesia Care, Microsoft Word, Medical-Surgical, Medication Administration, and Vital Signs. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate degree Nursing focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Cypress College.

Experience

St. Joseph Health Registered Nurse November 2018 - Present (1 year 9 months)

WHMC

Labor and Delivery Registered Nurse August 2016 - November 2018 (2 years 4 months)

Kindred Healthcare

LVN

September 2013 - September 2016 (3 years 1 month)

Santa Ana, California

Med/surg tele floor, patient care, medication administration, pro touch documentation.

Pain care providers

RN

May 2013 - August 2016 (3 years 4 months)

Irvine, California

Out patient surgery and doctor office specializing in pain management. Pre-Op and PACU RN.

Irvine endoscopy and surgical institue Lvn

September 2013 - September 2014 (1 year 1 month)
Outpatient surgery pre-op pacu

New Orange Hills LVN July 2011 - September 2014 (3 years 3 months)

Education

Western Governors University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2020)

Cypress College
Associate degree Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

North Orange County Regional Occupational Program LVN, Nursing Education · (2009 - 2010)

Golden West College

A.A, Math and Science, Communication · (2006 - 2008)